var myQuestions = [
	{
		question: "Foods high in saturated fats tend to raise",
		answers: {
			a: 'Blood Cholesterol',
			b: 'Blood Oxygen',
			c: 'Blood'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'a'
	},
	{
		question: "How many pounds of fat are needed to store 3500 calories",
		answers: {
			a: '10',
			b: '1',
			c: '5'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'b'
	},
	{
		question: "What is the strongest muscle in the body",
		answers: {
			a: 'Bicep',
			b: 'Heart',
			c: 'Pectorals'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'b'
	},
	{
		question: "Why is stretching important after a workout?",
		answers: {
			a: 'To make our muscles longer',
			b: 'To prevent diabetes',
			c: 'To relax strained muscles'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'c'
	},
	{
		question: "What does calcium do?",
		answers: {
			a: 'Works a 9-5',
			b: 'Makes Bones strong',
			c: 'Loves its wife'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'b'
	},
	{
		question: "Where is the largest bone in your body located?",
		answers: {
			a: 'Leg',
			b: 'Head',
			c: 'Toe'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'a'
	},
	{
		question: "Where is vitamin A primarily stored",
		answers: {
			a: 'Brain',
			b: 'Ear',
			c: 'Liver'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'c'
	},
	{
		question: "If you feel pain during exercise you should?",
		answers: {
			a: 'Keep going wimp',
			b: 'Cut off injured area',
			c: 'Stop the exercise'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'c'
	},
	{
		question: "How long should you warm up before exercising?",
		answers: {
			a: '10-15 minutes',
			b: 'Never since it wastes energy',
			c: '2 hours'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'a'
	},
	{
		question: "Approximately how much of your body weight is muscle?",
		answers: {
			a: '0%',
			b: '90%',
			c: '40%'
		},
		correctAnswer: 'c'
	},
